mrbookmarks.com 2013-05-30

# Manual Social Bookmarking Service Privacy and Refund Policy | Social Bookmarking Service

Privacy Policy:  
**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, chat with us or contact us!

When you order on our site you will be asked to enter your name, email, your website details to complete your order!

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

 **To complete your order:**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company

 **To send periodic emails:**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Refund Policy:**  
We do complete your order in 5-7 days, the order can take more days depending on the order volume.  
If we couldn’t do your job in a given timeframe, you can ask for the full refund and we will return your full amount to you.
